Ana Channel Applause.
Our guest today is this gentleman.
Hello! I'm Nana from Kororo Chiki Chiki Peppers! Please!
What are you wearing?
This is my outfit for fishing.
It has a light on it to illuminate it.
And, you know, I have a red one that shines when I make them listen to my voice.
And they like to dress up like that, you know, like, fishing, you know.
Anyway... you know... as you can see... I'm the type of comedian who gets taken advantage of... so... there was a little bit of uneasiness in the air.
You were on a fishing location, right?
That's right.
We were going fishing.
But there was a typhoon coming.
We couldn't make it.
We knew that early on.
But she came dressed like this.
But I couldn't think of anything to say to him.
I've been going around in circles.
What's that?
It's called a reel.
It's got a line on it.
You reel it in and reel in the fish.
And the other one? What about the main unit?
I don't understand why they canceled it because of the typhoon.
I'm not really into it. Forget it.
I'm halfway through reeling in the fish.
I was really planning on doing some fishing.
It's not what we planned. It's more like a surprise.
The set-up was more rushed than I expected, and it's not half bad, I'd say.
But I'm glad I got to see you for the first time in a while.
Yes, I see.
So, welcome to Anoland!
Let's make the most of it, this is the real deal! I'm doing something about it, too, because I can't help it.
Today I'm going to have you try out various games at Anoland.
Thank you very much.
Depending on how well each game is played, Nadare-san's fee will swing up the most to 3 percent.
Really? Really? You must be happy, right? Really? Really? You must be so happy. Thank you.
This is for real.
Really? I'm so happy.
You're so loud.
Sorry.
But it depends on how good the game is.
I know. The money is the most important thing, so I'm happy.
What if it doesn't work out?
If it doesn't work out, no money.
That's a lie!
You're lying!
I've been working a lot today.
But we'll pay you more, if you can make it.
I'll give it my best shot.
And there will be prizes.
Oh, really? That's great.
There will be prizes.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
My handmade prizes. My handmade expenses.
What? Her handmade expenses. I'm looking forward to it.
You think that's okay? I'm sorry, I'm not very good at this. It's just the two of us.
We don't have that, just the two of us, basically.
I'm not good at it. I'm sorry. I'm trying my best.
Now, let's go fishing with my special fishing rods.
When you catch a fish, you get the points written on the back.
You also get points depending on how well you play the game!
I'll do my best!
Some of them are lucky fish, and you get more money!
I found one that looks ridiculous.
I found one.
I'm just gonna go for it.
There's all kinds of fish here.
This is pretty good... a reel that winds a line.
It's really interesting.
You're a lefty.
Wow!
Hey. Hey.
I'm a lefty, too.
I'm a lefty, but I reel left-handed.
You understand?
Thank you.
Did you do this to Anu or anyone else?
I've made you whine a lot.
Yeah, well, thanks for telling me that.
Thank you, but I'll do my best.
You know Anu?
Of course I know Anu.
You've seen that Sosina thing, right?
Yeah.
I'm so happy to see Sosina looking so happy.
Awwwww!
She talks shit about him a lot.
He's a nice guy.
But she hates it when I say things like that.
I'm glad you were having fun.
Awwwwwww!
From hater to hater
He's a good guy, but he gets misunderstood
I'm gonna say something really nice
I'm gonna say it, I'm gonna say it
Well then, here's the challenge for you.
Okay, okay.
I'm not gonna lose.
You ready?
Okay, okay, let's do it.
On your marks.
All right, let's go.
Duda!
It's the other way around.
Wait a minute.
Yes!
I got it!
Yeah!
I swear to God, I can't open it. Can I open this?
Can I open it? Yes!
Oh, my God, this is the best thing ever.
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
You missed it!
You're so smart!
Wait a minute!
I kinda don't get this.
If only we had something that easy to understand now...
Oh, yeah, yeah...
That's hard.
It's hard, but hey!
You're a fisherman after all!
Here we go! Ready!
It says "5" in dirty handwriting.
What's this?
You didn't have time.
Five!
What's a five?
I don't know.
I don't know. I mean, the little one was so bad.
I think a big one might be better.
You don't know if a 5 is too much or too little.
It's so good!
I don't know.
It's got a lot of stuff on it.
Naoki Hanzawa's story
We had a tournament.
They're so quick to do it.
He has no hesitation at all... he did it on my box.
Really? It didn't look anything like it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Anna, why don't you try it?
I'll give you the shot.
Does that mean it's my score?
Good luck, Ana.
I don't remember which one I wrote, either. I don't remember which one I wrote on.
I bet you had to do a lot of coloring, didn't you?
It was a lot of work, wasn't it?
What's this?
Cosplay!
Cosplay?
You don't have any tools.
It's a costume.
Is it over there? Oh, no!
Costume play? Is it over there? Tight! Costume play?
We did the free stuff too.
You did the free stuff, too?
Costume play?
Sparkle!
But, you know, it's disgusting that the haters follow the haters.
It's the end of the line.
You know, following someone who's a jerk...
I can hear you.
That's the only place I can find someone to follow you.
I can't see you, though.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm at my limit, really.
It's done.
Here you go!
Next time, Ara, you'll look terrible.
What's that?
That was funny.
I was hoping you'd say who.
Who is it?
Zazie.
I told you.
Next.
That was really tough.
That was fun.
This is gonna break my heart.
May I? I'm trying to get paid more.
Yes! That was a funny episode. Oh, yeah! Interesting episode!
This is the staff's idea.
I'm going to show you a funny episode.
What's up? A funny story.
I went on a sales trip the other day.
I went to a business meeting at my alma mater.
I went to my alma mater to do some sales.
I said, "I'm doing business at my alma mater,
I was told to go home. I was away from home even at my alma mater.
At your alma mater? That's a lot.
That's right. It was tough.
Really, really, this is really hard.
The quality of the drawings and the selfishness is much tougher than I thought.
Oh my God, I don't know how much more I have to do to get paid for this!
Don't you have a clue?
I don't know either!
I still give it a 5.
I don't know... how many points do I get paid?
I don't know...
That's all you need.
To taste.
Taste?
Here we go!
Taste #5
Video X
I don't know.
What is this?
What is this, Video X?
Please ask them to take a video of you and then just take it.
I don't know... he said, "Please ask them to take a video together and then give it to them.
What a mess!
I knew that when you gave me those instructions.
What's that?
That's messy.
I heard the whole thing.
The channel's staff is messy.
I think you should fix it.
I think you should fix it. Can I take off my wig now?
Can I take my wig off? Can I take off my wig? I'm sorry, it's so hot I don't know what's wrong with me, but I think you should fix it.
Can I take the wig off?
Can I take the wig off? I'm sorry, it's so hot I don't know what to do.
This is so much easier.
I don't get it.
That's a little unfair.
That's funny.
It's tight. It's really tight.
Cute.
Cute and tight, really cute and tight.
Can I borrow this for a second?
Chinese pervert.
What are you filming?
I'm sorry, Haru. I had to ask you to turn it.
I'm sorry, Haru-chan, but I had to ask you to turn it.
What are you doing, Al?
Al-chan! Al-chan!
I wonder if I can catch it
I don't think you'll catch it.
Al!
Al, this is really good. I'm not good at this. Are you going to put it on now?
It's night like this, I can't think straight.
It's not easy.
It's nighttime.
They're gonna push me, man.
They say I'm so unmotivated.
Shit, I needed some advice.
Advice on the video.
I'm never going to get it right if I do it off the cuff.
He talks so much!
Okay, let's go to the X's.
It's done!
I've been dropped!
I've been dropped! It's hard to get dropped.
I'm thinking about it and now I have to do this.
My heart is breaking
That post is kinda harsh...
Then it's still 5 points!
You've got a lot of work to do, Ano.
It doesn't lead to a score at all, you know.
Not yet, but there's a high score in there, too.
I saw that the small ones were the ones that got the highest scores,
I was aiming for something too big. The big ones have a lot of space to write.
That's right.
Oh, double the size!
That's amazing!
How is that possible?
I'm so happy. I think it's going to happen.
I think it's going.
It's a little bit of one.
One and... what's this?
The money's up!
Fifty!
50!
We're fresh! I got 50!
I got 51!
No increase in pay.
No! No?
Not yet.
Not yet? Because we don't know how many points.
It's transmitting a lot smaller than it is right now.
Come closer.
That's right.
Maybe this one, too.
30!
Eighty-six.
More and more numbers.
40! 100 points!
126 points!
Yay! Yay!
I didn't get the character up.
Wait, wait, wait!
I don't know the rules!
The rules are so hard to understand!
I'm so disappointed when I don't get my character up!
I love your point of view!
Thank you very much.
Your eyes are so big!
Oh, my God, it's a go, but...
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I'm getting good at emotions.
I think I'm going to pinch everything!
I'm getting used to it.
Thank you.
I'm very careful with these things.
Okay, bye.
Back up a few points... -20.
-Twenty.
I've been away for a while... but it's hard to find a place like this.
I've been going on location for a while now.
I don't go fishing anymore.
I'm sure Bali would be happy if I did this with the kids.
I'm sure he'd be happy to do this with his kids.
I don't know about this, but I don't know how the viewers feel about it.
I don't know, but I wonder how the viewers feel about this.
I'll hook this hook or hook this hook.
Can't you sleep through this?
In a china dress.
I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared all the time.
Maybe I should change my aim.
Okay, here we go.
Thirty!
That's great! That's great!
We got it! We got it back!
A big, big one!
It comes in two different colors and is a bit expensive.
What? This is a big one with two different colors and a little expensive.
I was in the top of the competition in the Hanshin Cup, and everyone was gasping for air, and then I was asked to do some kind of gag, and I couldn't do it!
The customers were also being asked to do the same thing, and those who could do the continuous ayin would raise their hands and the camera would go in on them and do the continuous ayin, but the customers were not so hard on them, so they didn't really care.
But the audience is not so demanding, so they don't get it, and when they do this, some of them get it and some of them get it and some of them get it and some of them get it and some of them get it and some of them get it.
And then at the end, Nadasu-san's continuous "yabba yabba yabba," and I slipped to my death, and 50,000 people booed me, and I slipped even at a site with such low hurdles.
It was tough.
Oh, man!
Yes, I did.
So, I was thinking...
You'd better stop playing "Oh, shit!
Don't tell me I'm gonna have to stop doing that, ano.
And now for the last one.
Let's go with the octopus.
I'm going to try octopus.
I knew it! It's a little embarrassing!
I'm a little embarrassed.
I don't have time for this, so please do a better job with the editing.
Okay, I'll go.
I'll go from here.
It's stuck!
Like this...
What's this?
Small talk.
What kind of small talk was that?
Motonae
Don't say bad things on the radio anymore, what kind of small talk were you talking about? Shohin-e
Don't say such bad things on the radio, you'll soon become internet news.
I'm worried about you. You're funny as hell, but...
I hope everyone likes you, for God's sake.
Twenty points.
20 points for a little comment.
The final score is...
161 points. I got a lot of points. 161 points. I got a lot.
I almost got it. How about this?
I don't get paid more. I don't understand.
How many more games did I have to play before I get paid? I'm just sweating.
No, we're almost there. We have another game to play.
Okay, I'll give it my best shot.
But I'll give it my best shot, but here's the game score, Aron-chan's score.
Nazart's score.
I think it's really a 2.
It's a two.
It took me a while to get there.
It's true that there were some parts that I couldn't watch.
The clips.
The hook.
I'd do it with you.